Guide to the Joseph V. Charyk papers, 1957-1989 MS2137
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Administrative files, 1962-1989; MS2137 Series 1; 29 Linear feet (Box 12, Box 11, Box 10, Box 9, Box 55, Box 35, Box 53, Box 54, Box 51, Box 52, Box 38, Box 50, Box 40, Box 39, Box 42, Box 41, Box 44, Box 43, Box 46, Box 45, Box 47, Box 48, Box 49, Box 58, Box 57, Box 56, Box 5, Box 6, Box 7, Box 
  - Filing [1/3], 02/23/1983-04/15/1983 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Filing [2/3], 02/28/1983-04/06/1983 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Filing [3/3], 02/24/1983-03/18/1983 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Finance - Business Travel SPI 30 - 44, 11/13/1979-12/15/1980 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Financial Records, 10/20/1982-03/02/1984 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Financial Statements, 12/31/1967-02/23/1968 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Financial Vice President (Recruitment), 01/05/1970-04/26/1970 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Financial World August 1, 1979, 08/01/1979 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - First Annual Meeting of Shareholders, 08/01/1964-09/17/1964 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Forbes - April 14, 1980, 04/14/1980 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Ford Aerospace & Communications Corporation [1/2], 12/15/1982 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Ford Aerospace & Communication Corporation [2/2], undated (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Freedom Expression Foundation Inc., 01/20/1983-01/21/1983 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - GEOSAT, 10/06/1976-10/15/1976 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Historical Documents, 01/11/1963-03/01/1963 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Historical Documents [2/2], 02/18/1963-06/23/1965 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Historical Documents [3/3], 01/31/1963-05/06/1964 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - History of COMSAT, 11/17/1982-08/08/1984 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - H.R. 13015, 08/02/1978-08/11/1978 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - IBM Word Processing, 10/12/1976-11/03/1976 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - "Information Technologies and Social Transformation" 1985 [1/2], 10/04/1984-02/01/1985 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - "Information Technologies and Social Transformation" 1985, 10/04/1984-12/11/1984 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - INMARSAT, 1975-04/29/1981 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - INMARSAT Bill 1977, 10/14/1977 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - INMARSAT - Implementation of Section 505 of the International Maritime Satellite Communications Act, 02/22/1980 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - INMARSAT - International Conference of the establishment of an International Maritime Satellite System 1975 - 1976, undated (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - INTELSAT 1971 - 1974 [1/2], 08/13/1973-10/14/1974 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - INTELSAT 1971 - 1974 [2/2], 12/24/1970-07/30/1973 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - INTELSAT Meeting of Signatories, undated (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - INTELSAT Signatories' Reception and Dinner, Sunday Apr. 8, 1984, 03/14/1984 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - INTELSAT Operating Agreements [1/3], undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - INTELSAT Operating Agreements [2/3], undated (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - INTELSAT Operating Agreements, undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - INTELSAT Mgt. Services Contract (Corresp. with S. Astrain), 12/08/1971-03/08/1977 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - INTELSAT Meeting of Signatories/Assembly of Parties Tehran, Iran April 1978, 08/16/1973-03/14/1978 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - INTELSAT Meeting of Signatories (No. 6) Sydney, Australia (April 1977), 12/15/1976-05/10/1977 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - INTELSAT Meeting of Signatories Washington, DC Nov 12 - 15, 1973, 09/25/1973-01/14/1974 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - INTELSAT Meeting of Signatories 1974 [1/2], 01/31/1974-06/21/1974 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - INTELSAT Meeting of Signatories 1974 [2/2], 10/25/1973-01/07/1974 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - INTELSAT Meeting of Signatories 1975 [1/3], 11/15/1973-04/21/1975 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - INTELSAT Meeting of Signatories [2/3], 02/21/1975-04/02/1975 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - INTELSAT Meeting of Signatories 1975 [3/3], 11/12/1973-03/03/1975 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - INTELSAT Meeting of Signatories/Assembly of Parties Safari - Kenya Sept. 1976 [1/2], 07/26/1976-01/04/1977 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - INTELSAT Meeting of Signatories/Assembly of Parties Safari - Kenya Sept. 1976 [2/2], 07/27/1976-09/30/1976 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - INTELSAT Fourth Meeting of Signatories Singapore April 1976, 03/03/1976 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - INTELSAT Meeting of Signatories Acapulco, Mexico April 1974, 02/14/1974-04/03/1974 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - INTELSAT Third Meeting of Signatories Montreal April 1 - 4, 1975, 10/04/1974-04/17/1975 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - INTELSAT VI Procurement [1/2], 02/03/1982-03/17/1982 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - INTELSAT VI Procurement [2/2], 11/05/1981-02/02/1982 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - An Intercity Telecommunictions Business Assessment, 07/20/1983 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - International Matters, 12/11/1963-11/30/1970 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - International Legal Considerations Relating to Direct Broadcast Satellites [1/2], 03/18/1980 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - International Legal Considerations Relating to Direct Broadcast Satellites [2/2], 03/18/1980 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - International Telecommmunications Deregulation Act of 1982, 05/14/1982 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Johnson, John A., 08/29/1980-09/04/1981 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Land Remote Sensing Commercialization Act of 1984, 09/15/1984 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Landon School Nov. 18, 1964, 08/24/1964-08/27/1964 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Launch Vehicle, 06/11/1975-08/02/1976 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Leaders - July, Aug, Sept 1981, 07/20/1981-09/1981 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Legal: Gerity v Cable Funding [1/3], 05/14/1973-02/24/1975 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Legal: Gerity v Cable Funding [2/3], 12/06/1973-12/17/1974 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Legal: Gerity v Cable Funding [3/3], 12/04/1973-03/29/1974 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Management Report (COMSAT), 05/09/1980 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Management Resources Planning, 07/30/1976-05/22/1980 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Marketing Handbook, undated (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Market Research Study, 08/04/1972 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - McConnel Memoranda 1970 - 1974, 05/25/1970-09/05/1975 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - McDonnell Douglas Suit 1970 - 1971, 05/27/1970-01/18/1971 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - McGraw, Richard, 08/08/1985 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Memo Harrington 1977 re:echo canceller, 02/24/1977 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Memos - "Unsoliceted memos gifts", 06/04/1964-08/25/1964 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Merger Legislation, 10/30/1968-09/18/1969 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Metzger Memos, 05/10/1967-07/11/1969 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous 1979, 09/1978-06/15/1984 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous 1982 - 1984, 12/30/1982-09/25/1984 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous 1983 [1/4], 05/02/1983-08/24/1983 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous [2/4], 02/22/1983-03/23/1983 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous 1983 [3/4], 01/14/1983-03/08/1983 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous 1983 [4/4], 07/21/1983-06/24/1985 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous 1983 - 1985 [1/2], 02/08/1983-01/31/1985 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous 1983 - 1985 [2/2], 01/19/1983-06/04/1985 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous 1984 [1/2], 06/22/1983-10/12/1984 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous 1984 [2/2], 12/06/1984-10/07/1981 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous II, 04/24/1967-04/15/1968 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous III, 07/07/1967-07/07/1976 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - [Miscellaneous IV], 10/12/1971-04/26/1973 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Nascom Services Chron. Summary, 07/26/1965-11/23/1965 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - National Foreign Trade Council Nov. 17, 1964, 09/25/1964-12/1964 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Navy Maritime Proposal, 03/03/1973-04/19/1973 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - NIPPON Electric Co., Ltd (NEC) [1/2], 09/1979-12/04/1980 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - NIPPON Electic Co., Ltd (NEC) [2/2], 08/27/1979-10/06/1980 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - NITELSAT Venture Analysis, 07/31/1970 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Nolebook [Notebook?] Meetings [1/5], 08/31/1962-01/25/1966 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Nolebook [Notebook] Meetings [2/5], 11/23/1963-12/17/1964 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Nolebook [Notebook?] Meetings [3/5], 04/06/1964-01/25/1966 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Nolebook [Notebook?] Meetings [4/5], 03/07/1963-06/15/1964 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Nolebook [Notebook?] Meetings [5/5], 10/23/1963-07/28/1964 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - NTIA COMSAT Work Study, 09/17/1979-03/29/1981 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - NTIA Study on Pro-Competitive International Initiatives [1/2], 08/20/1981 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - NTIA Study on Pro-Competitive International Initiatives [2/2], 07/23/1981 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - The Opportunity for Facsimile, 09/12/1975 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Overhead Cost Reduction - 1981, 07/09/1981-09/01/1981 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Personnel - 1966 [1/3], 01/17/1966-12/30/1966 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Personnel - 1966 [2/3], 04/13/1966-10/11/1966 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Personnel - 1966 [3/3], 01/09/1964-05/09/1966 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Personnel - 1967 [1/2], 03/06/1967-12/12/1967 (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Personnel - 1967 [2/2], 01/03/1966-03/30/1967 (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Personnel - 1968 [1/2], 11/25/1968-05/05/1969 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Personnel - 1968 [2/2], 01/25/1968-11/21/1968 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Personnel - 1969, 04/15/1969-01/02/1970 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Personnel - 1970, 12/03/1969-09/16/1970 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Personnel 1971 - 1974, 07/18/1973-01/02/1975 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Personnel 1971 - 1974 [2/2], 12/07/1970-04/08/1974 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Personnel Actions [1/2], 06/10/1967-11/13/1970 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Personnel Actions [2/2], 05/24/1967-06/22/1967 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Personnel Bartle-Schwartz, undated (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Personnel Goals and Calculations of Performance Units, 02/15/1983-03/01/1983 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Personnel Metzger, Sydney, 01/25/1982-05/16/1985 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Photographs [1/3], undated (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Photographs [2/3], undated (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Photographs [3/3], undated (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Project Satellite, undated (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Project Satellite - Supplementary Materials, undated (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Prospectus, 06/02/1964 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - R&D Policy Committee, 12/30/1980-06/11/1981 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - RARC 1983 - Regional Administrative Radio Conference [1/2], 01/09/1980-09/21/1982 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - RARC 1983 [2/2], 03/25/1981 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Rate Reduction 1971, 04/28/1971-06/23/1971 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Record Retention Schedule, undated (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Remote Sensing Business Development Team, 02/07/1984 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Research and Development (Laboratories), 01/20/1983-02/22/1984 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Revised Job Descriptions, 01/12/1984 (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Round Table Group (Metropolitan Club), 09/22/1964 (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - SAIPAN Earth Station Dedication, 11/02/1980 (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - SBS (Satellite Business Systems) [1/2], 12/27/1983-06/22/1984 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Satellite Business System (SBS) [2/2], 01/22/1980-11/24/1980 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - SBS December 1975, 12/03/1975-12/02/1976 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - SBS January - February 1976, 11/27/1975-05/21/1976 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - SBS March - May 1976, 12/19/1975-09/16/1976 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - SBS June - September 1976, 02/19/1976-09/22/1976 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - SBS June - October 1979, 06/1979-10/11/1979 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - SBS 1983, 12/12/1983 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Satellite Communications The Impact of Space Science on Mankind Plenum Press, New York, 1976, undated (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Satellite Television Corporation [1/2], 02/1984-10/02/1984 (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Satellite Television Corporation [2/2], undated (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Satellite Week April 14, 1980, 04/14/1980 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Schematic Evolution, undated (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Senate Foreign Relations Committtee 1983 [1/2], 07/23/1981-10/31/1983 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Senate Foreign Relations Committee 1983 [2/2], 04/15/1983-10/31/1983 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Senior Management Handbook, Planning Process 1985, 06/1984 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Solo Sapiens, 10/01/1982 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Sonnenfeldt, Richard W., 1981-01/15/1985 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Space Policy Act, 10/11/1978-12/01/1981 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - SPARX, 01/06/1984-01/24/1984 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Spencer Stuart and Associates [1/2], 08/17/1981-11/03/1982 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Spencer Stuart and Associates [2/2], 06/1981-05/05/1982 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Statements of Interest (By-Laws Requirements) [1/3], 03/28/1968-10/10/1969 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Statements of Interest (By-Laws Requirements) [2/3], 03/24/1965-01/17/1968 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Statements of Interest (By-Laws Requirements) [3/3], 06/30/1964-10/31/1966 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Strategic Directions, 06/1984 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Technical Advisory Committee, 02/05/1985-05/16/1985 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Technical-Economic Cte Meeting [1/2], 11/18/1975-01/15/1976 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Technical-Economic Cte Meeting [2/2] January 15, 1976, 12/05/1975-01/12/1976 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Telecommunications Establishment in The People's Republic of China, 08/1979 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Telecommunications Proposal, 03/09/1984 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Theodore Von Karman Professorship, 01/05/1978-12/29/1978 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - UNISPACE '82 - Vienna, Austria [1/3] August 9 - 12, 1982 World Systems Division, 08/09/1982-08/12/1982 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - UNISPACE '82, 02/13/1982-11/04/1982 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - UNISPACE '82, 06/1982-08/21/1982 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - U.S.S.R., 07/1977-11/22/1978 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - United States Exhibition in Beijing 1984 [/2] January - March 1982, 03/02/1982-03/26/1982 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - United States Exhibition Beijing 1984 [2/2] January - March 1982, 12/09/1981-03/03/1982 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - United States Exhibition in Beijing 1984 [1/2] April - June 1982, 05/04/1982-06/30/1982 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - United States Exhibition in Beijing 1984 [2/2] April - June 1982, 04/05/1982-05/11/1982 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - United States Exhibition in Beijing 1984 July - September 1982, 07/06/1982-09/24/1982 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - United States Exhibition in Beijing 1984 October - December 1982, 10/04/1982-12/30/1982 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - United States Exhibition in Beijing 1984 January - March 1983, 01/10/1983-05/29/1987 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - White & Case 1984, 09/26/1984 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - World Communications Year 1983 [1/2], 10/01/1982-09/13/1983 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - World Communications Year 1983 [2/2], 07/30/1981-04/30/1982 (Box 58, Folder 3)
- Organizations, 1957-1970; MS2137 Series 2; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 60, Box 59)
  This series contains brochures, and reports. The mterial dates from 1957-70. The material relates to many of the organizations Charyk and COMSAT collaborated with.
  - Organizations -- ABC - ITT Merger 1967, 04/10/1967-04/14/1967 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Organizations -- AIAA 1966, 05/18/1965-05/10/1968 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Organizations -- Miscellaneous, 08/1969-03/1970 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Organizations -- Aerojet - General Corporation, 12/16/1968 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Organizations -- Aeronautical Radio, Inc., undated (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Organizations -- Aerospace Corporation 1965 - 1969, 12/17/1965-07/28/1969 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Organizations -- Aerospace Medical Association, undated (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Organizations -- Air France, 07/27/1966 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Organizations -- Air Transport Association, 06/12/1970 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Organizations -- Airtronics Incorporated 1968 - 1969, undated (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Organizations -- American Bar Associations 1969, 04/15/1969 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Organizations -- American Broadcasting Company, Inc. 1969, 11/05/1969 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Organizations -- American Institute of Certified Public Accountants 1966, 08/16/1965 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Organizations -- American Management Association 1967, 08/26/1965-10/20/1965 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Organizations -- American Management Association Inc. 1968 - 1972 [1/2], undated (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Organizations -- American Management Association Inc. 1968 - 1972 [2/2], undated (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Organizations -- American Management Association Inc. 1968 - 1971, 02/23/1967-06/1969 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Organizations -- American Newspapers Publishers Association 1967, 06/26/1967-02/16/1970 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Organizations -- American Society of Interpreters 1969, 07/03/1969 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Organizations -- American Society of Mechanical Engineers 1968, 03/07/1968 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Organizations -- Advance Technology Corporation 1967, 03/06/1967 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Organizations -- American Telephone & Telegraph 1962 - 1965, 1957-08/18/1965 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Organizations -- American University 1969, 02/1969-01/19/1970 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Organizations -- American Women in Radio and Television, Inc. 1969, 06/30/1967 (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Organizations -- Armed Forces Management Associaton 1965, 12/04/1965 (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - Organizations -- Arthur Anderson & Co. 1968, 01/06/1968 (Box 59, Folder 26)
  - Organizations -- Atomic and Space Development Authorities 1966, 03/31/1965 (Box 59, Folder 27)
  - Organizations -- Automated Offshore Navigation 1971, undated (Box 59, Folder 28)
  - Organizations -- Babson & Co. Inc. David L. 1969, 04/29/1969 (Box 59, Folder 29)
  - Organizations -- Bankers Trust New York Corp. 1967, undated (Box 59, Folder 30)
  - Organizations -- Basic International Research Center 1966, 03/03/1966 (Box 59, Folder 31)
  - Organizations -- Batelle Memorial Institute 1967, 02/19/1965-10/31/1967 (Box 59, Folder 32)
  - Organizations -- Beckman 1965, 01/22/1965 (Box 59, Folder 33)
  - Organizations -- Bell Systems 1965, 03/09/1965 (Box 59, Folder 34)
  - Organizations -- Bell Telephone Laboratory 1963 - 1969, 09/13/1969-02/20/1969 (Box 59, Folder 35)
  - Organizations -- Blonder Tongue 1966, 09/29/1966 (Box 59, Folder 36)
  - Organizations -- Boeing 1967, 02/27/1967 (Box 59, Folder 37)
  - Organizations -- The Bridge 1968, 02/02/1968-10/11/1968 (Box 59, Folder 38)
  - Organizations -- British Aircraft Corporation 1969, 02/1969 (Box 59, Folder 39)
  - Organizations -- British Broadcasting Company 1967, 05/19/1967 (Box 59, Folder 40)
  - Organizations -- Brookings Institute 1968, 05/18/1968-06/17/1970 (Box 59, Folder 41)
  - Organizations -- Brown & Sons, Alex 1966, 06/01/1966-09/21/1966 (Box 59, Folder 42)
  - Organizations -- Builders Estimating Service, Inc. 1965, 05/10/1965 (Box 59, Folder 43)
  - Organizations -- BIRPI International 1968, 10/30/1968 (Box 59, Folder 44)
  - Organizations -- Business Jets 1965 - 1966, 04/15/1966 (Box 59, Folder 45)
  - Organizations -- Business Week 1966, 05/18/1965 (Box 59, Folder 46)
  - Organizations -- Butler National Corporation 1967, 09/13/1967-01/05/1968 (Box 59, Folder 47)
  - Organizations -- CEIR Inc. 1968, 01/22/1965 (Box 59, Folder 48)
  - Organizations -- C.L. Carter Jr. & Associates 1969, 12/31/1968-01/03/1969 (Box 59, Folder 49)
  - Organizations -- California Insitute of Technology 1966 - 1967, 11/1966 (Box 59, Folder 50)
  - Organizations -- International Center at Canisy [1/2], undated (Box 59, Folder 51)
  - Organizations -- International Center at Canisy [2/2], undated (Box 59, Folder 52)
  - Organizations -- Cavisat 1969, 06/16/1969-06/19/1969 (Box 59, Folder 53)
  - Organizations -- Centre D'Eudes Industrielles 1968, 05/1968 (Box 59, Folder 54)
  - Organizations -- Centre International du Canisy 1966, 08/13/1965-12/14/1966 (Box 59, Folder 55)
  - Organizations -- Chamber of Commerce 1966, 09/22/1966-10/11/1966 (Box 59, Folder 56)
  - Organizations -- Checche and Company 1965, 12/14/1965 (Box 59, Folder 57)
  - Organizations -- Citiel 1967, 10/27/1967 (Box 59, Folder 58)
  - Organizations -- Comparisons & Evaluations User Reaction Analysis 1966, undated (Box 59, Folder 59)
  - Organizations -- Communications Comparisons and Evaluations 1966, 10/30/1963-05/13/1966 (Box 59, Folder 60)
  - Organizations -- Comparisons & Evaluations User Research Analysis 1966, 02/17/1966-08/1966 (Box 59, Folder 61)
  - Organizations -- CEPT 1971, 01/25/1971 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Organizations - CEPT 1968, 08/16/1968-09/03/1968 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Organizations -- CEPT (Meeting) 1966, 01/06/1964-02/09/1966 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Organizations CEPT Bonn Meeting 1963, 11/26/1963 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Organizations CEPT 1965, 07/13/1965-08/02/1965 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Organizations Alaska Universal Telephone Co., 1966-1968 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- Conferences, symposiums, and seminars, 1961-1983; MS2137 Series 3; 2.5 Linear feet (Box 62, Box 61, Box 60)
  This series contains brochures, lectures, reports, and letters. The material is dated from 1961-83. This material relates to many of the conferences, symposiums and seminars that Charyk attended and/or participated in while working for COMSAT.
  - Von Karman Lecture 1961, 05/11/1961 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - St. Mary's College Executive Symposium, 11/11/1963-12/10/1964 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - University of Alberta May 27, 1964, 04/27/1964-05/13/1968 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Los Angeles Rotary Club 1965, 03/29/1965-06/15/1965 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - French IEEE [Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers, inc.] Pans 1965, 02/03/1965 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Symposium of Reliability and Quality Control January 12, 1965, 09/03/1964-04/1965 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - IEEE [Institute of Electrical and Electronics Engineers, inc.] Conference February 3-5, 1965, 11/24/1964-01/21/1965 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Rochester Engineering Society Feb. 17, 1965, 10/26/1964-02/26/1965 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - AFC&E [Armed Forces Communications and Electronics Association] February 24, 1965, 07/21/1964-01/22/1965 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Governor's Conf. on Science and Technology Maui, Hawaii Jan. 26-30, 1965 [1/2], 01/29/1965-06/02/1965 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Governor's Conf. on Science and Technology Maui, Hawaii Jan. 26-30, 1965 [2/2], 01/28/1965-02/05/1965 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Monetary Conference American Bankers Association Princeton, NJ March 17, 1965, 01/19/1965-03/17/1965 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Distinguished Lecture Series (Catholic University) March 24, 1965, 10/16/1964-03/29/1965 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Economic Club of Oklahoma April 19, 1965, 10/01/1964-04/09/1965 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - St. Louis Bicentennial Space Symposium May 28, 1965, 02/24/1965-03/18/1966 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - AIAA [American Institute of Aeronautics and Astronautics] Luncheon June 3, 1965, 02/08/1965-06/03/1965 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - D.C. Bankers Assoc. Convention The Greenbrier June 9-13, 1965, 03/17/1965-06/28/1965 (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - XIII International Congress on Communication Genoa, Italy Oct. 12-16, 1965, 01/22/1965-10/20/1965 (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Commercial Club of Chicago Feb. 10, 1966, 11/19/1965-02/15/1965 (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - National Assoc. [Association] of Broadcasters Chicago March 30, 1966, 03/25/1966-04/08/1966 (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - National Assoc. [Association] of Manufacturers Washington, D.C. June 7, 1966, 04/12/1966-06/16/1966 (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Bell Labs Operating Engineers Training Prog. Oct. 18, 1966, 04/29/1966-10/05/1966 (Box 60, Folder 28)
  - Cal Tech 75th Anniversary Los Angeles Oct. 25, 1966, 08/05/1966-11/02/1966 (Box 60, Folder 29)
  - 3rd General Assembly Asian Broadcasting Union Taipei Oct. 24-29, 07/11/1966-11/24/1966 (Box 60, Folder 30)
  - Town Hall Los Angeles Nov. 8, 1966, 02/10/1966-01/23/1967 (Box 60, Folder 31)
  - Institute of Life Insurance New York City Dec. 13, 1966, 06/27/1966-01/10/1967 (Box 60, Folder 32)
  - Canadian Club Montreal Canada Feb. 27, 1967, 08/29/1966-03/08/1967 (Box 60, Folder 33)
  - Canadian Society of Exploration Geophysicists Calgary Frebruary 28, 1967, 12/21/1966-03/17/1967 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - DACOR Washington, DC March 9, 1967, 09/19/1966-03/28/1967 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Senior Seminar in Foreign Policy Washington, DC May 18, 1967, 03/08/1967-06/09/1967 (Box 61, Folder 3)